Guide to the Rabbi Arthur Schneier Papers TAM.694
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II. International and Domestic Events, 1956-2016, undated; 8 audiocassettes; 1 film reels; 1 VHS; 53.52 Gigabytes in 6,374 computer files.; 26.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 53 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 2.5 small flat boxes, and 1.5 media boxes.
  - Subseries II.A. Conferences, Summits, and Forums, 1956-2015, undated; 6 audiocassettes; 1 VHS; 1 film reels; 44.58 Gigabytes in 4,704 computer files.; 18 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 29 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 2.5 small flat boxes, and 1 media box.
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Correspondence, undated; 2 folders (Box 30, Folder 3, 9)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Images, undated; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Images -- Madrid, Spain
      - Digital Images, TW_TAM_694_ER_48
      - Prints (Box 147, Folder 27)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Information Packet, undated; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Itinerary and Invitation, undated; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: List of Invitees, 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Notes, undated; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Press Releases, 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Press Releases and Contact Information, 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Program and Agenda, undated; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Speeches and Papers
      - Digital Files, TW_TAM_694_ER_47
      - Paper Files (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - 2008 World Conference on Dialogue: Video Recordings, TW_TAM_694_ER_46
    - 2009 Bet El Yeshiva Center Dinner: Correspondence, Photographs, and Press, 2008-2009; 1 folder (Box 279, Folder 10)
    - 2009 Cathedral Gala: Photographs -- at Plaza Hotel, undated; 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 28)
    - 2009 Conference of the Presidents Leadership Delegation to the Vatican: Correspondence, Media Advisory, and Press, 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 23)
    - 2009 Conference of the Presidents Leadership Delegation to the Vatican: Itineraries, Correspondence, and List of Recipients of the Pope and Rabbi Arthur Schneier's Remarks, 2009, undated; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - 2009 Conference of the Presidents Leadership Delegation to the Vatican: Luggage Tags, Correspondence, List of Delegates, and Menu, 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - 2009 Conference of the Presidents Leadership Delegation to the Vatican: Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with the Pope, 2009, undated; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - 2009 Conference of the Presidents Leadership Delegation to the Vatican: Press, 2 folders (Box 212, Folder 20, 21)
    - 2009 Conference of the Presidents Leadership Delegation to the Vatican: Speeches and Press, 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 22)
    - 2009 Conference of the Presidents Leadership Delegation to the Vatican: Video Recording, TW_TAM_694_ER_100
    - 2009 Constantinople Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew I Visits PES: Photographs and Images, undated; 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - 2009 Constantinople Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew I Visits PES: Press, Invitation, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 18)
    - 2009 Constantinople Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew I Visits PES: Programs, Brochures, Correspondence, and Press, 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 17)
    - 2009 Lefkovits and Spector Families Torah Dedication: Correspondence and Photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 246, Folder 27)
    - 2009 Luncheon on the Occasion of the Enthronement of Patriarch Kirill and in Honor of the Visit of Rabbi Arthur Schneier: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - 2009 Luncheon on the Occasion of the Enthronement of Patriarch Kirill and in Honor of the Visit of Rabbi Arthur Schneier: Menu, Invitations, and Guest Lists, 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - 2009 Mayor Nir Barkat Visit at PES: Images, 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - 2009 Papal Visit to Israel of His Holiness Pope Benedict XVI: Correspondence, 2008-2009; 2 folders (Box 107, Folder 13, 23)
    - 2009 Papal Visit to Israel of His Holiness Pope Benedict XVI: Photographs and Images, 2009, undated
      - Digital Images, TW_TAM_694_ER_23
      - Prints (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - 2009 Papal Visit to Israel of His Holiness Pope Benedict XVI: Press, 2 folders (Box 107, Folder 11, 12)
    - 2009 Papal Visit to Israel of His Holiness Pope Benedict XVI: Press, Images, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - 2009 Papal Visit to Israel of His Holiness Pope Benedict XVI: Program, Pamphlet, Correspondence, Schedule, and Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - 2009 Patriarch Bartholomew Visits PES: Images and Video Recordings, TW_TAM_694_ER_58
    - 2009 Patriarch Bartholomew Visits PES: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - 2009 Private Audience at Vatican with Pope Benedict XVI: Photograph and Images, undated; 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - 2009 Reception for Mayor Nir Barkat of Jerusalem at PES: Program, Press, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - 2009 Retirement Ceremony for Ambassador Ruth Davis: Correspondence and Photograph, 2009, undated; 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - 2009 Visit to England: Correspondence, Menu, Schedule, and Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - 2009 Visit to Poland: Itinerary, Press, Speech, Invitations, Brochure, and Concert Program, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - 2009-2010 Visit to Morocco, Switzerland, Austria, Hungary, France, and Italy: Event Guest List and Correspondence -- Morocco, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - 2009-2010 Visit to Morocco, Switzerland, Austria, Hungary, France, and Italy: Correspondence -- About Hungary, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - 2009-2010 Visit to Morocco, Switzerland, Austria, Hungary, France, and Italy: Correspondence -- The Vatican, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - 2009-2010 Visit to Morocco, Switzerland, Austria, Hungary, France, and Italy: Correspondence, Menu, and Lists of Guests, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - 2009-2010 Visit to Morocco, Switzerland, Austria, Hungary, France, and Italy: Images, 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - 2009-2010 Visit to Morocco, Switzerland, Austria, Hungary, France, and Italy: Itinerary, Schedule, Press, and Guest Lists, 1 folder (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - 2009-2010 Visit to Morocco, Switzerland, Austria, Hungary, France, and Italy: Schedule, Itinerary, Contacts, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - 2009-2010 Visit to Morocco, Switzerland, Austria, Hungary, France, and Italy: Photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - 2009-2010 Visit to Morocco, Switzerland, Austria, Hungary, France, and Italy: Press, 7 folders (Box 226, Folder 2-5, Box 108, Folder 3, 4, Box 239, Folder 1)
    - 2010 Archbishop of New York Timothy Dolan Visits PES: Photographs, Correspondence, and Press, 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 24)
    - 2010 Archbishop of New York Timothy Dolan Visits PES: Photographs and Images, 2010, undated
      - Digital Images, TW_TAM_694_ER_57
      - Prints (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - 2010 Archbishop of New York Timothy Dolan Visits PES: Photographs and Images -- Unveiling of Plaque Commemorating the First Papal Visit to an American Synagogue, TW_TAM_694_ER_56
    - 2010 Bono Visits PES: Images, undated
      - Digital Images, TW_TAM_694_ER_66
      - Prints (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - 2010 Croatian Independence Day: Correspondence, Press, and Speeches, 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 22)
    - 2010 Dinner in Honor of the Italian President of the Chamber of Deputies Gianfranco Fini: Speech, Video Recordings, and Photographs
      - Digital Files, TW_TAM_694_ER_87
      - Paper Files (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - 2010 Luncheon with Dr. Joseph Deiss at PES: Correspondence and Invitation, 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 21)
    - 2010 Luncheon with Dr. Joseph Deiss at PES: Images and List of Guests, undated
      - Digital Images, TW_TAM_694_ER_53
      - Paper Files (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - 2010 PES 120th Anniversary and Rabbi Arthur Schneier's 80th Birthday Celebration: Images, 2010, undated
      - Digital Images, TW_TAM_694_ER_55
      - Prints (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - 2010 PES 120th Anniversary and Rabbi Arthur Schneier's 80th Birthday Celebration: Video Recordings -- Tribute to Rabbi Arthur Schneier, TW_TAM_694_ER_73
    - 2010 PES 120th Anniversary and Rabbi Arthur Schneier's 80th Birthday Celebration: Video Recording, Correspondence, Press, and Lists of Guests, 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 23)
    - 2010 Performance of the Terezin Cantata: Program and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 279, Folder 8)
    - 2010 Religious Freedom Turkey's Bridge to the European Union Conference: Program, Speech, Correspondence, Notes, Press, and Contact Information, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - 2010 The Roma of Europe - The Europe of Roma Conference: Program, Correspondence, and Remarks, 1 folder (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - 2010 Visit to China: Images, 2010, undated; 2 folders (Box 148, Folder 7, 16)
    - 2010 World Summit of Religious Leaders in Baku, Azerbaijan: Correspondence, List of Attendees, Speeches, and Travel Information, 1 folder (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - 2011 150th Anniversary of Italian Unification Luncheon: Correspondence and Photographs, 1 folder (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - 2011 2600th Anniversary of Buddhist Enlightenment Ceremony at the United Nations: Images, undated
      - Digital Images, TW_TAM_694_ER_69
      - Prints (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - 2011 2600th Anniversary of Buddhist Enlightenment Ceremony of the United Nations: Transcript, Program, Press, Correspondence, and Images, 1 folder (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - 2011 2600th Anniversary of Buddhist Enlightenment Ceremony at the United Nations: Video Recordings, TW_TAM_694_ER_68
    - 2011 Grand Order of King Dmitar Zvonimir with Sash and Star Ceremony: Correspondence and Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 25)
    - 2011 Grand Order of King Dmitar Zvonimir with Sash and Star Ceremony: Order Decision and Announcement of Order, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 26)
    - 2011 Grand Order of King Dmitar Zvonimir with Sash and Star Ceremony: Press, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 27)
    - 2011 Istanbul World Political Forum: Correspondence, 2010-2011; 2 folders (Box 29, Folder 7, 8)
    - 2011 Istanbul World Political Forum: Images
      - Digital Images, TW_TAM_694_ER_103
      - Prints (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - 2011 Istanbul World Political Forum: Itinerary and Travel Information, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - 2011 Istanbul World Political Forum: Notes and Booklet, undated; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - 2011 Istanbul World Political Forum: Press Releases, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 2011 Istanbul World Political Forum: Programs and Name Tags, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - 2011 Istanbul World Political Forum: Report, Biographical Information, and Articles, 2009-2011; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - 2011 Istanbul World Political Forum: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - 2011 Jan Karski U.S. National Centennial Inaugural Dinner: Correspondence, Handouts, Video Recording, and Image Files, 2007-2014; 1 folder (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - 2011 PES Annual Awards Dinner: Images and Video Recordings
      - Digital Files, TW_TAM_694_ER_22
      - Paper Files (Box 246, Folder 29)
    - 2011 PES Annual Awards Dinner: Images, Press, and List of Park East Day School Attendees, 1 folder (Box 278, Folder 15)
    - 2011 PES Carl Lutz Commemoration: Press, Correspondence, and Invitation, 1 folder (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - 2011 United States Department of State Meetings and Woodrow Wilson Award Dinner: Schedule, Correspondence, Invitation, and Biographical Information, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 2011 Visit to Austria and Turkey: Images -- Vienna, Austria and Istanbul, Turkey, 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - 2011 Visit to Vienna, Austria: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - 2011 Woodrow Wilson Center for International Scholars in Washington, D.C. Awards Dinner: Video Recordings, TW_TAM_694_ER_28
    - 2012 50th Anniversary of Rabbi Arthur Schneier at PES: Press, Formal Invitations, Images, and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 18)
    - 2012 50th Anniversary of Rabbi Arthur Schneier at PES: Press, Images, Video Recordings, Speeches, Schedule, Correspondence, Guest Lists, and Seating Information
      - Digital Files, TW_TAM_694_ER_85
      - Paper Files (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - 2012 Bar Mitzvah for Brendan Isaac: Invitation and Guest Lists, 1 folder (Box 278, Folder 14)
    - 2012 Istanbul World Political Forum: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 2012 Istanbul World Political Forum: List of Speakers, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - 2012 Istanbul World Political Forum: Program, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - 2012 Istanbul World Political Forum: Wikipedia About Article, 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - 2012 Meeting with Bosnia-Herzegovina Delegation at PES: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - 2012 Ukrainian Council of Churches and Religious Organizations Visits PES: Program and Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 278, Folder 13)
    - 2012 UN World Interfaith Harmony Week: Program, Speeches, List of Participating Organizations, and Speakers, 1 folder (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - 2012 UNESCO's High Panel on Peace and Dialogue Among Cultures: Correspondence -- Reception in Honor of Rabbi Arthur Schneier, 1 folder (Box 249, Folder 16)
    - 2012 UNESCO's High Panel on Peace and Dialogue Among Cultures: Correspondence, Press, and Lists of Participants, 1 folder (Box 249, Folder 17)
    - 2012 UNESCO's High Panel on Peace and Dialogue Among Cultures: Invitation, Schedule, Itinerary, Menu, and Notes, 1 folder (Box 249, Folder 18)
    - 2012 UNESCO's High Panel on Peace and Dialogue Among Cultures: Press, Program, List of Participants, and Notes, 1 folder (Box 249, Folder 21)
    - 2012 UNESCO's High Panel on Peace and Dialogue Among Cultures: Speech, 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - 2012 UNESCO's High Panel on Peace and Dialogue Among Cultures: UNESCO Publications, 2010-2012; 2 folders (Box 249, Folder 19, 20)
    - 2012 Visit to Bosnia and Herzegovina: Correspondence -- Srebrenica Genocide Commemoration, 2 folders (Box 101, Folder 22, Box 102, Folder 6)
    - 2012 Visit to Bosnia and Herzegovina: Correspondence, Embassy Packet, Commemoration Addresses -- Srebrenica Genocide Commemoration, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - 2012 Visit to Bosnia and Herzegovina: Embassy Packet, Commemorative Addresses, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - 2012 Visit to Bosnia and Herzegovina: Guest List -- American Ambassador's Reception in Honor of Rabbi Arthur Schneier, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - 2012 Visit to Bosnia and Herzegovina: Images -- Srebrenica Commemoration and Rabbi Arthur Schneier Reception, TW_TAM_694_ER_8
    - 2012 Visit to Bosnia and Herzegovina: Press -- Srebrenica Genocide Commemoration, 4 folders (Box 236, Folder 9-12)
    - 2012 Visit to Bosnia and Herzegovina: Speeches and Speaker's Biographical Information -- Srebrenica Genocide Commemoration, 1 folder (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - 2012 Visit to Bosnia and Herzegovina, Hungary, and Austria: Schedule and List of Gifts, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - 2012 Visit to France, Switzerland, Bosnia and Herzegovina, Hungary, and Austria: Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - 2012 Visit to South Korea: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - 2012 Visit to South Korea: Correspondence, Programs, Gifts for Hosts, Schedule, and Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - 2012 Visit to South Korea: Press and Handouts, 2012, undated; 1 folder (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - 2013 Lantos Foundation Conference on Jewish Life and Anti-Semitism in Contemporary Europe: Correspondence, Speeches, Schedule, and Program, 1 folder (Box 273, Folder 14)
    - 2013 PES and ACF Sponsored Forbidden Art Exhibition at PES: Flyers, Correspondence, Invitations, Speeches, and Guest List, 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - 2014 90th Birthday Celebration for Yugoslavian Minister of Foreign Affairs Budimir Loncar: Flyer, Invitations, Name Cards, and Menu, 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - 2014 Dialogue between the Appeal of Conscience Foundation and the McCain Institute's Next Generation Leaders: Correspondence and Flyers, 1 folder (Box 273, Folder 15)
    - 2014 Meeting of the American Jewish Committee: Speech -- Bartholomew, Ecumenical Patriarch, 1 folder (Box 247, Folder 17)
    - 2014 The Meeting of Pope Francis and Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew in the Holy City of Jerusalem: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - 2014 The Meeting of Pope Francis and Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew in the Holy City of Jerusalem: Press, 1 folder (Box 237, Folder 12)
    - 2014 The Meeting of Pope Francis and Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew in the Holy City of Jerusalem: Schedule, Itinerary, Programs, Photographs, and Video Recording, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - 2014 The Meeting of Pope Francis and Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew in the Holy City of Jerusalem: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 237, Folder 13)
    - 2014 Visit to the Czech Republic: Press, Correspondence, and Booklets, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - 2014 Visit to the Czech Republic: Schedule, Brochure, Notes, and Press, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - 2014 Visit to Poland and Italy: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - 2014 Visit to Poland and Italy: Itinerary, Schedule, Notes, Event Guest List, and Handouts, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - 2014 Yom Kippur Event at PES: Flyer, Correspondence, Speeches, Handouts, and Press, 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - 2015 Anti-Defamation League A Tribute to Abraham H. Foxman: Booklet, Program, and Menu, 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - 2015 High-Level Thematic Debate Promoting Tolerance and Reconciliation: Speeches, Correspondence, and Press, 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - 2015 Visit to Switzerland, Morocco, and Austria: Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 18)
    - American Friends of Lubavitch Event: Photographs -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Vladimir Putin, undated; 1 folder (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - Campaign for a Rabbi for United States Embassy in Moscow: Press and Correspondence, 1973, undated; 1 folder (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - Campaign to Save Mukachevo Jewish Cemetery: Correspondence, 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 18, 19)
    - Campaign to Save Mukachevo Jewish Cemetery: Lists of Relatives and Photographs, undated; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 16, 17)
    - The Ditchley Foundations Conference on the Search for an Arab-Israeli Settlement: Conference Material, Correspondence, Foundation Reports, and Notes, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Enthronement of Patriarch Kirill: Notes, 2009; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Enthronement of Patriarch Kirill: Press Releases and Photograph, 2009; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - The Europe of Roma Conference: Name Tag -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, undated; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - Freedom of Faith Conference: Correspondence, 2011; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - International Prayer for Peace: Press Releases, 2006; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Interreligious Dialogue at the Cervantes Institute: Press Releases, 2007; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - Islam in a Pluralistic World Conference: Press Releases, 2005; 2 folders (Box 40, Folder 12, 13)
    - The Leningrad Eleven Protest: Correspondence, Reports, and Press, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 228, Folder 1, 2)
    - Plenary Meeting of the United Nations General Assembly Under Agenda Item 45 "Culture of Peace": Program of Meetings and Agendas, 2008; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Plenary Meeting of the United Nations General Assembly Under Agenda Item 45 "Culture of Peace": Speeches, 2008; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Romanian Rabbi Moshe Rosen Receives Honorary Doctorate from Yeshiva University: Photographs -- Rosen, Rabbi Moshe with Rabbi Arthur Schneier and President Rabbi Lamm, circa 1986; 1 folder (Box 238, Folder 24)
    - Second World Congress of Imams and Rabbis for Peace: Correspondence, 2006; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Second World Congress of Imams and Rabbis for Peace: Informational Printout, 2006; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - The Stockholm International Forum: Contacts, Schedule, List of Delegations, and Press, 2004; 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 12)
    - The Stockholm International Forum: Correspondence, 2004; 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 11)
    - The Stockholm International Forum: List of Delegates, Schedule, and Coverage of Workshops -- U.S. Delegation, 2004; 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 14)
    - The Stockholm International Forum: List of Delegates, Statements, Reports, and Fact Sheets, 2004; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - The Stockholm International Forum: Papers, Correspondence, and Transcribed Presentations, 2004; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - The Stockholm International Forum: Schedules, Statements, and Workshop Information, 2004; 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 10)
    - The Stockholm International Forum: Statement -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 2004; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - The Stockholm International Forum: Statements, Remarks, and Papers, 2004; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - The Stockholm International Forum: Statements and Workshop Information, 2004; 1 folder (Box 240, Folder 13)
    - Tenth Anniversary of the Dayton Peace Accord: Press Releases, 2005; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Third Corporate Dinner Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, INC.: Program and Guest List, 1978; 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - United Nations Alliance of Civilizations Meeting: Press Releases, 2006; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - UNESCO General Conference: Agenda, Speeches, and News Articles, 2003; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - United States Holocaust Memorial Museum Opening Events: Information Packet, 1986-1993, undated; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Visit to Austria: Sound Recording, undated (Box 255, Cassette 694.0023)
    - World Conference on Religion and Peace Symposium: Information Packet, 2001; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Yeshiva University 70th Annual Hanukkah Convocation and Dinner: Correspondence and Photographs, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Subseries II.B. Commemorative Events, 1976-2016, undated; 1.83 Gigabytes in 71 computer files.; 4 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes.
    This subseries contains pamphlets, photographs, images, programs, correspondence, speeches, press clippings, and video recordings of commemorative remembrance events. The bulk of the material from this subseries comes from Holocaust Remembrance events held at PES and the United Nations. Some material in this subseries is in Bosnian, Hungarian, or Hebrew. There are born-digital media--video, image, and document files--in this subseries.
    The material in this subseries is grouped chronologically by date of event, then arranged alphabetically by type.
    - 1976 Memorial Service for Jews from Czechoslovakia-Nazi Victims: Invitation, 1 folder (Box 238, Folder 28)
    - 1976 Warsaw Ghetto Memorial: Correspondence and List of Guests, 1 folder (Box 284, Folder 36)
    - 1983 40th Anniversary American Gathering of Holocaust Survivors: Invocation and Press, 1 folder (Box 277, Folder 34)
    - 1984 Commemoration of the 40th Anniversary of the Deportation of the Hungarian Jews: Program, Handouts, Correspondence, and Press, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 229, Folder 17)